你能和天使交流
So, you talk to angels?
我只能偷听
I just overhear them.
我们终于知道恶魔们为什么那么想你死
Now we know why the demons want you so bad.
这是尤瑞尔  一位专家
This is uriel, a specialist.
又见到你了 迪恩
Hello again, dean.
不认识我了么
Don't you recognize me?
在地狱里我们可走的很近
But we were so close... in hell.
阿拉斯泰尔
Alastair.
-他们来了  -到里屋去
They're coming. back room!
我们来这里是为了安娜
We're here for anna.
你们是来帮助她的吗
Are you gonna help her?
她必须得死
She has to die.
你们要安娜
You want anna?
为什么
Why?
不关你的事
Out of the way. whoa, whoa, whoa.
我知道她偷听你们天使聊天什么的
Okay, I know she's wiretapping your angel chats or whatever,
但这也不是让你们俩个送她归西的理由啊
But it's no reason to gank her.
别担心  我会让她平静的死去
Don't worry. I'll kill her gentle.
你们真他妈的冷血知道不
You're some heartless sons of bitches, you know that?
事实上我们就是
As a matter of fact, we are.
还有什么废话要说
And?
安娜是无辜的
And anna's an innocent girl.
她一点也不无辜
She is far from innocent.
你这话什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
她比这个魔鬼小妞更不值得你们在她身上浪费时间
It means she's worse than this abomination you've been screwing.
现在把她交给我们
Now give us the girl.
抱歉
Sorry.
想都别想
Get yourself another one.
试试吧 你个傻叉
Try jdate.
谁能阻止我们  你们俩
Who's gonna stop us? you two?
要么这个恶魔婊子吗
Or this demon whore?
卡西迪奥 住手
Cass, stop...please.
我等这刻很久了
I've been waiting for this.
怎么回事
What the...
起来
Come on.
安娜
Anna.
Anna!
他们走了没
Are they -- are they gone?
你杀了他们吗
Did you kill them?
没
No.
我把他们传送走了
I sent them away...
很远的地方
Far away.
能告诉我怎么做到的
You want to tell me how?
我脑子里突然出现的
That just popped in my head.
我不知道怎么做到的
I don't know how I did it.
我就是做到了
I just did it.
你怎么认为
So, what do you think?
我觉得安娜越来越不可思议了
I think anna's getting more interesting by the second.
我同意
Yeah, I agree.
他们说"她不是无辜的"是什么意思
And what did they mean by "she's not innocent"?
他们只是想要她死
It seems like they want her bad,
不只是因为那天使热线的原因
And not just 'cause of the angel radio thing.
我想 那个血咒什么的 这事挺严重的 伙计
I mean, that blood spell -- some serious crap, man.
她身上一定发生过什么
Something's going on with her.
-试试你能查到什么  -你打算怎么办
See what you can find out. what are you gonna do?
安娜也许把天使送到很远  但迟早
Anna may have sent the angels to the outfield, but, sooner or later,
他们会回来的
They're gonna be back.
我们要找个安全的地方
We got to get ourselves safe now.
铁墙中间含盐
Iron walls drenched in salt.
恶魔们别想进来这地方
Demons can't even touch the joint.
顺便说一下  这是种族歧视
Which I find racist, by the way.
写信给你的国会议员
Write your congressman.
拿着
Here.
魔咒袋
X bags?
额外保护
Extra-crunchy.
能帮我们躲过天使恶魔和所有来访者
They'll hide us from angels, demons, all comers.
谢谢 露比
Thanks, ruby.
别丢了
Don't lose this.
安娜  天使热线有没有播放一些
So, anna, what's playing on angel radio?
有用的消息吗
Anything useful?
没声音
It's quiet.
一片死寂
Dead silence.
很好
Good.
麻烦解决了
That's not troubling at all.
我们会有麻烦么
We're in trouble, huh?
你们害怕了
You guys are scared?
没有
Nah.
嘿 迪恩
Hey, dean!
呆在这里
Just stay here, okay?
看住她
Keep an eye on her.
车怎么样了
How's the car?
拿到了 没事
I got her. she's fine.
鲍比在那里
Where's bobby?
在多米尼加
The dominican.
他说我们弄坏任何东西都要赔的
He said we break anything, we buy it.
-他在工作  -我希望是
He's working a job? god, I hope so.
要不然骗我们在外面穿性感内裤鬼混
Otherwise, he's at hedonism in a banana hammock and a trucker cap.
我不想去幻想
Now that's seared in my brain.
关于安娜 有什么发现没
What did you find on anna?
不多
Uh, not much.
她父母叫瑞奇和艾米 米尔顿  一个教会执事的和家庭主妇
Her parents were rich and amy milton -- a church deacon and a housewife.
-听起来不错 -不错
Riveting. yeah.
但报告的这里说
But there is something here in the report.
-这不是她第一次闹剧  -什么不是
Turns out this latest psych episode wasn't her first. no?
当她2岁半的时候  他爸一靠近她  他就发疯
When she was 2 1/2, she'd get hysterical any time her dad got close.
她认定那不是他亲身父亲
She was convinced that he wasn't her real daddy.
谁才是  那个水管工
Who was? the plumber, hmm?
管道工的阳物?（黄色笑话）
A little snaking the pipes?
你的疑惑又联想到色情的事情
Dude, you're confusing reality with porn again.
安娜没说
Look, anna didn't say.
她只是说他真正的父亲很生气
She just kept repeating that this real father of hers was mad.
非常生气  那种气到要杀她的程度
Very mad -- like wanted-to-kill-her mad.
对2岁的孩子太严重了
Kind of heavy for a 2-year-old.
她去看了儿童心理医生  并一点点好转
Well, she saw a kid's shrink, got better, and grew up normal.
直到现在  她隐瞒了什么
Until now. so, what's she hiding?
为什么你们不直接问我
Why don't you just ask me to my face?
看她看的真好
Nice job watching her.
我正在看着她
I'm watching her.
你说的对 安娜
No, you're right, anna.
有什么要告诉我们的么
Is there anything you want to tell us?
关于什么
About what?
天使说你有罪
The angels said you were guilty of something.
他们为什么这么说
Why would they say that?
你告诉我
You tell me.
告诉我我的生活为什么会改变
Tell me why my life has been leveled...
为什么我的父母会死
Why my parents are dead.
我不知道
I don't know.
我发誓
I swear.
要我做什么都好  我也很想知道
I would give anything to know.
好吧
Okay.
让我们查个水落石出
Then let's find out.
怎样查
How?
我们来了
We're here!
帕梅拉 嘿
Pamela. hey.
-萨姆  -是我  萨姆
-Sam. -it's me. it's sam.
-萨姆  -是我
-Sam? -yeah.
萨姆 是你吧
Sam, is that you?
我在
I'm right here.
知道我怎么认出你吗
Know how I can tell?
是你的小屁屁告诉我的
That perky little ass of yours.
用它都能弹硬币玩
You could bounce a nickel off that thing.
我当然知道是你  臭小子
Of course I know it's you, grumpy.
我还知道那是个恶魔  还有可怜的小安娜
Same way I know that's a demon, and that poor girl's anna.
你还一直看我
And that you've been eyeing my rack.
别紧张  孩子
Don't sweat it, kiddo.
-我比一般人敏感多了  -确实
-I still got more senses than most. -You got it.
安娜
Hey, anna.
你好吗  我是帕梅拉
How are you? I'm pamela.
迪恩已经把发生的事告诉我了
Dean told me what's been going on.
我非常想帮你
I'm excited to help.
谢谢你
Oh. that's nice of you.
其实也不是
Oh, well, not really.
只要能把天使揪出来  任何机会我都不放过
Any chance I can dick over an angel, I'm taking it.
为什么
Why?
他们从我身上偷走了东西
They stole something from me.
恶魔眼  我知道
Demon-y, I know.
不过它们是塑料的  这样比较好做生意
But they're just plastic. good for business.
让人觉得我有特殊灵力  你觉得呢
Makes me look extra-psychic, don't you think?
那就让你自己告诉我发生了什么
Now...how about you tell me what your deal is?
别担心
Don't you worry.
躺好放松
Nice and relaxed.
现在我开始倒数5秒
Now, I'm going to count down from five to zero.
当我数到0  你就进入深度睡眠
When we're at zero, you'll be in a deep state of hypnosis.
我倒数的时候  越来越深  好吗
As I count down, just go deeper and deeper, okay?
五
5...
四
4...
三
3...
二
2...
一
1.
沉睡吧
Deep sleep.
放松每一寸肌肉
Every muscle calm and relaxed.
能听到我吗
Can you hear me?
我能听到
I can hear you.
现在  安娜  告诉我
Now, anna, tell me...
你怎么听到天使讲话的
How can you hear the angels?
你当时是怎么施法的
How did you work that spell?
我不知道
I don't know.
我就是会
I just did.
你父亲
Your father...
他的名字是
What's his name?
瑞奇·米尔顿
Rich milton.
很好
All right.
再往前回想
But I want you to look further back...
你小的时候
When you were very young...
几岁大的时候
Just a couple of years old.
我不要去想
I don't want to.
没事的
It'll be okay.
安娜  看一下就好  我们想要的就这些
Anna, just one look -- that's all we need.
不
No.
你爸爸叫什么名字
What's your dad's name?
你的亲生父亲
Your real dad.
他为什么冲你发火
Why is he angry at you?
不
No. no!
No.
不
No!
冷静  他会杀了我的
Calm down. he's gonna kill me!
安娜  你很安全
Anna, you're safe.
冷静
Calm down.
他会杀了我的
He's gonna kill me!
-安娜  -迪恩  别过来
-Anna? -dean, don't.
醒过来  1  2  3  4  5
Wake in 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
安娜
Anna...
你还好吧
You all right?
谢谢你  帕梅拉
Thank you, pamela.
这很有用
That helped a lot.
我想起来了
I remember now.
想起了什么
Remember what?
我是谁
Who I am.
我被雷到了 你到底是谁
I'll bite. who are you?
我是个天使
I'm an angel.
别害怕  我和别人不一样
Don't be afraid.i'm not like the others.
我不太相信
I don't find that very reassuring.
我也不
Neither do i.
那么  卡西迪奥和尤瑞尔 他们是来找我的吧
So...castiel, uriel -- they're the ones that came for me?
你认识他们
you know them?
我们是一队的
We were kind of in the same foxhole.
他们是你老大或者其他
So, what, they're like your bosses or something?
反过来想呢
Try the other way around.
看看你
Look at you.
可现在他们想杀了你
But now they want to kill you?
命令就是命令
Orders are orders.
我确定我被判了死刑
I'm sure I have a death sentence on my head.
为什么
Why?
我抗命了
I disobeyed...
对我们来说  这是最严重的事情
Which, for us, is about the worst thing you can do.
我堕落
I fell.
意味着
Meaning?
她落到地上  变成人类
She fell to earth, became human.
等下  我不明白
Wait a minute. I don't understand.
天使能变成人吗
So, angels can just become human?
会有些痛苦
It kind of hurts.
和用刀把肾割下来的感觉差不多
Try cutting your kidney out with a butter knife.
那种痛苦
That kind of hurt.
我剥离了我的能量
I ripped out my grace.
再说一遍
Come again?
我的能量
My grace.
就是能量
It's...energy.
没有它就会掉下来
Hacked it out and fell.
我妈妈  艾米  没法怀孕
My mother, amy, couldn't get pregnant.
总说我是她的奇迹小宝贝
Always called me her little miracle.
她不知道她说的有多贴切
She had no idea how right she was.
那么 你只是忘了你是上帝手下的特种部队
So, you just forgot that you were god's little power ranger?
活得越久 我就越以为自己是人类 是的
The older I got, the longer I was human, yeah.
我认为你们还没意识到我们创了个多大的祸
I don't think you all appreciate how completely screwed we are.
露比是对的 天堂那边想让我死
Ruby's right. heaven wants me dead.
而地狱只是想得到她
And hell just wants her.
一个可以审问的 折磨的 活生生的天使 我同情你
A flesh-and-blood angel that you can question, torture, that bleeds.
姐们儿 你就是那耀眼的斯坦利杯（北美职业冰联盟总冠军）
Sister, you're the stanley cup.
而且不管天堂还是地狱 迟早他们都会找到你
And sooner or later, heaven or hell, they're gonna find you.
我知道
I know.
这就是为什么我要把它还回去
And that's why I'm gonna get it back.
你说什么
What?
我的能量
My grace.
你能那么做吗 如果我能找到它
You can do that? if I can find it.
所以呢 那你要抽神赐的大麻 然后施展魔咒
So, what, you're just gonna take some divine bong hit, and, shazam,
你以为自己是罗玛·唐尼（主演《我和天使有个约会》）
You're roma downey?
差不多吧
Something like that.
好吧 我喜欢这个计划
All right. I like this plan.
那么 你的那些能量在哪里
So, where's this grace of yours?
来的时候弄丢了
Lost track.
那时我坠落的速度大概每小时1万英里
I was falling about 10,000 miles per hour at the time.
等一下 你是说坠落 就像我们常说得那样吗
Wait. you mean falling, like, literally?
是的
Yes.
就像人类经常可以看到的方式吗
Like the way a human eye can see?
像是一个彗星或是流星吗
Like a comet maybe or a meteor?
你为什么这么问
Why do you ask?
这里
Here.
85年3月
In march '85,
一颗流星消失在俄亥俄州西北部的夜空
A meteorite vanished in the night sky over northwestern ohio.
那出现得比安娜出生的早9个月
It was sighted nine months before anna was born,
而且就出生在俄亥俄的那个地区
And she was born in that part of ohio.
你真是针强心剂
You're pretty buff for a nerd.
想想吧 我想那就是安娜
Look, I think it was anna.
并且在这里 同一时间 肯塔基出现另一颗流星
And here, same time -- another meteor over kentucky.
那就是她的能量吗
And that's her grace?
有可能是
Might be.
好吧
All right.
那只是把范围缩小到了一个州
That just narrows it down to an entire state.
想想吧 这只是个开始
Look, it's a start.
萨姆 对不起
Sam...i'm sorry.
为什么
For what?
给你带来这个大麻烦
For bringing you this mess.
如果我早知道 我一定会闭口不谈
If I had known, I would have kept my trap shut.
好吧 我们会对付过去的
Yeah, well, we'll muddle through.
这次恐怕不行
Not this time.
你不会想夹在这两方之间的
You do not want to get between these two armies.
他们是哥斯拉和巨蛾（1964年的电影）
It's godzilla and mothra.
即使一方找不到我们 另一方也会的
If one side doesn't get us, the other one will.
那么 你想怎么做 丢下安娜自己跑路吗
So, what do you want to do? dump anna and run?
算了吧
Forget it.
我知道天使们把你惹毛了
Look, I know the angels freak you out.
忘了那些天使吧 我真正怕的是那个阿拉斯泰尔
Forget the angels. it's alastair I'm scared of.
阿拉斯泰尔 你在教堂里见过他
Alastair? you met him in the church.
实际上是地狱里来的傲慢的判官
Practically the grand inquisitor downstairs.
使剃刀的毕加索
Picasso with a razor.
还有呢
And?
还有你应该把他揪出来 丢回到他来的地方...
And you should pull him out and throw him back in the pit...
如果不是你变得那么虚弱 露比...
If you weren't so out of shape. ruby...
不 你的能力 你正在变得虚弱
No, your abilities -- you're getting flabby.
是啊 我该如何恢复能力呢
Yeah, so how do I tone up?
你知道怎样做
You know how.
你知道你应该怎么做
You know what you got to do.
不 我再也不要那么做了
No, I'm not doing that anymore.
好吧 那你最好祈祷安娜可以找回她的能量
Well, then you better prr pray that anna gets her groove back,
不然我们都得死
Or we're all dead.
帕梅拉回家了吗
Pamela get home okay?
是的 她说她很抱歉
Yeah. she said she was sorry.
只是从上一次开始 她 就...
It's just after last time, she, uh...
这一切对她来说太难了
This is just a little too rich for her blood.
我不怪她
I don't blame her.
你们也该那么做
You guys should do the same.
我们没那么聪明
Well, we're not that smart.
我能问你些问题吗
Can I ask you something?
他们想让我做什么呢
What do they want me for?
他们为什么要救我
Why did they save me?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
天使们没有说起过这件事
The angels aren't talking about it.
而且那是我坠落之前的事了
And it was after I fell.
还有个问题
That's another question.
你怎么会坠落呢
Why would you fall?
你为什么要成为我们中的一员呢
Why would you want to be one of us?
你不会明白的
You don't mean that.
我不会吗
I don't?
一群卑劣的低等动物...
A bunch of miserable bastards...
吃饭 拉屎 迷惑 恐惧
Eating, crapping, confused, afraid.
我不明白
I don't know.
这里还有忠诚...
There's loyalty...
宽容...
Forgiveness...
爱
Love.
-痛苦 -巧克力蛋糕
Pain. chocolate cake.
-罪恶 -性爱
Guilt. sex.
是啊 你找对人了
Yeah, you got me there.
我是认真的
I mean it.
各种情感 迪恩 即使是不好的...
Every emotion, dean, even the bad ones...
...这就是我坠落的原因
...it's why I fell.
这就是为什么...
It's why...
这就是为什么我要放弃一切也不要回去
Why I'd give anything not to have to go back.
一切
Anything.
如果你问我 我会说你高估了那些感觉
Feelings are overrated, if you ask me.
总比做天使好
Beats being an angel.
那怎么可能
How's that possible?
你们充满力量而且完美
You guys are powerful and perfect.
你不怀疑你自己或是上帝或是任何事
You don't doubt yourselves or god or anything.
完美
Perfect...
像个大理石的雕像
Like a marble statue.
冰冷的...
Cold...
没有选择的...
No choice...
只有服从
Only obedience.
迪恩 你知道有多少天使真正见过上帝吗
Dean, do you know how many angels have actually seen god?
看到他的脸吗
Seen his face?
你们全部都见过
All of you?
只有四个天使
Four angels.
四个
Four.
而我不是其中之一
And I'm not one of them.
就因为这样吗
That's it?
好吧  那你们怎么知道究竟存不存在上帝
Well, then how do you even know that there is a god?
我们必须有信仰
We have to take it on faith...
如果我们不相信  我们会被杀死
Which we are killed if we don't have.
我驻扎在人间2000年
I was stationed on earth 2,000 years.
只是 看着
Just...watching...
无声
Silent...
无形
Invisible...
永远都在路上
Out on the road...
厌倦故乡
Sick for home...
永远都在等待
Waiting on orders
来自那个我无法了解的
from an unknowable father
也不知道存不存在的上帝的命令
I can't begin to understand.
所以不要告诉我 有什么好笑的  怎么了
So don't tell me that -- what is so funny? what?
没什么  不好意思
Nothing. sorry.
只是...
It's just...
我知道这种感受
I can relate.
你查到什么了吗
Did you find something?
我想是的
I think so.
尤宁，肯塔基州
Union, kentucky.
我找到一些关于当地奇幻事件的记录
Found some accounts of a local miracle.
1985年  小镇外有一片空地
In '85, there was an empty field outside of town.
6个月之后变成了茂密的橡树林
Six months later, there was a full-grown oak.
他们说那些橡树看起来至少有1000年了
They say it looks a century old at least.
安娜  你觉得呢
Anna, what do you think?
我的能量
The grace.
被它撞到的地方
Where it hit
都会发生这样类似的事情  很简单
it could have done something like that, easy.
所以当你的力量砸到地面
So grace ground zero
不会造成破坏  这是...
it's not destruction. it's...
百分百的创造
Pure creation.
怎么了
What?
没什么
Nothing.
只是一个天使和一个魔鬼同时坐在后座
It's just an angel and a demon riding in the backseat.
好像是一个故意安排的恶作剧
It's like the setup to a bad joke...
或者是色情小说
Or a penthouse forum letter.
伙计
Dude...
现实点...
Reality...
色情文学
Porn.
你称这个是现实
You call this reality?
真美
It's beautiful.
我的能量就是降落到了这里
It's where the grace touched down.
我能感觉到
I can feel it.
准备好了吗
You ready to do this?
还没
Not really.
安娜  你到底是在找什么
Anna, what are we even looking for?
这不重要
It doesn't matter.
它不再这
It's not here.
已经不在这里了
Not anymore.
有人把它拿走了
Someone took it.
我说我们回那个避难所吧
I say we head back to the panic room.
什么  难道永远都躲在这儿
What, forever?
我只是想得太大声了
I'm just thinking out loud!
你说刚才那叫思考
Oh, you call that thinking?
停战
Hey! hey, hey, hey. stop it.
安娜的能量不见了  你明白吗
Anna's grace is gone. you understand?
她不能变成天使  她不能保护我们
She can't angel up. she can't protect us.
我们不可能同时与天堂和地狱交战
We can't fight heaven and hell.
一个一个来也许还行  但是不能同时
One side maybe, but not both. not at once.
伙计们
Um...guys?
天使又在说话了
The angels are talking again.
他们在说什么
What are they saying?
好奇怪...
It's weird...
好像是录音...
Like a recording...
是循环的
A loop.
迪恩 温彻斯特在午夜前把安娜给我们  否则...
It says, "dean winchester gives us anna by midnight, or..."
否则什么
Or what?
否则我们把它丢回地狱的深渊
"or we hurl him back to damnation."
安娜...
Anna...
你知道有什么武器对天使有效吗
Do you know of any weapon that works on an angel?
干什么  杀了他们吗
To what? to kill them?
我们没有办法...
Nothing we could get to...
现在不行
Not right now.
好吧  等等  我说我们打电话给鲍比
Okay, wait, wait. I say we call bobby.
让他回来  不要在外面风流了
We get him back from hedonism.
迪恩  他能知道什么我们还不知道的东西
Dean, what's he gonna tell us that we don't already know?
我不知道  但是我们总得想点什么啊
I don't know, but we got to think of something!
怎么样了
Holding up okay?
正努力呢
Trying.
有点害怕  我想
A little scared, I guess.
那么...
So, um...
迪恩...
Dean...
我只是想要谢谢你
I just wanted to thank you.
因为什么
For what?
所有的一切
Everything.
你们  你们本不用帮我
You guys -- you didn't have to help me -- hey,
不要再说些"谢谢你""努力了"的话了  知道吗
Let's can the "thanks for trying" speech, you know?
我们什么屌忙都没帮上
Participation trophies suck ass.
我不知道
I don't know.
也许我不该得到救赎吧
Maybe I don't deserve to be saved.
不要这么说
Don't talk like that.
我抗命了
I disobeyed.
路西法也抗命了
Lucifer disobeyed.
这是我们最大的死罪  我知道
It's our murder one, and I knew it.
也许我必须偿还
Maybe I got to pay.
是啊  好吧  每个人都干过需要付出代价的事情
Yeah, well, we've all done things we got to pay for.
我得告诉你一些事
I got to tell you something.
你不会喜欢的
You're not gonna like it.
好吧  是什么
Okay. what?
大约一个礼拜前  我听到天使在说
About a week ago, I heard the angels talking...
关于你的事
About you...
你在地狱的所作所为
What you did in hell.
迪恩  我知道
Dean, I know.
这不是你的错
It wasn't your fault.
你应该原谅你自己
You should forgive yourself.
安娜  我不想
Anna, I don't w-want to, uh...
我不想
I don't want to...
我不能说
I can't talk about that.
我知道
I know.
但是当你能说的时候
But when you can
你身边有想要帮你的人
you have people that want to help.
你不是孤身一人
You are not alone.
那是所有我想说的
That's all I'm trying to say.
那是为什么
What was that for?
你知道...
You know...
这是我们在人间的最后一晚上...
Our last night on earth...
就那样
All that.
你抢了我的拿手戏
You're stealing my best line.
i'm walking down this rocky road
wondering where my life is leading
rolling on to the bitter end
i'm finding out along the way
what it takes to keep love living
you should know how it feels,my friend
oooh
i want you to stay
i want you today
i'm ready for love
oh, baby, i'm ready for love
ready for love
yeah
oh-oh-oh
for your love
好啊  露比
Hello, ruby.
阿拉斯泰尔
Alastair.
不得不说  看到你在人间的这副样子还真是意外啊
I have to say, I'm surprised to find you out in the open like this.
是吗
Yeah?
正逢乱世
Desperate times.
确实如此
That they are.
在找这个吗
You looking for this?
你那愚蠢人类朋友把这给了我
Your gawky human friend gave it to me.
自个儿留着吧
Keep it.
我只是来聊聊的
I just came to talk.
聊什么
About what?
有关恶魔怎么保护天使吗
About how a demon is protecting an angel?
我们真该把你除名了
We really must revoke your membership.
听着  我知道这几月未能尽职
Look, I know I'm not employee of the month,
但这趟浑水  我真不想搅进来
But this -- I never wanted to get in the middle of this.
那你为啥在这儿呢  露比
Why are you here, ruby?
我会把天使交给你
I'll give you the angel.
是吗
Will you?
做为交换呢
And in return?
重获自由
I walk away.
我还有温彻斯特俩兄弟
Me and the winchester boys, both of them.
天使的事不关我们的事
This angel business is none of our business.
知道吗
You know...
我早听说过你是个奸诈胆小的小泼妇了
I'd always heard that you were a devious, cowardly little slut.
百闻不如一见
You don't disappoint.
你意下如何
So, what do you say?
还真有趣
It's interesting...
小心点
Prudent.
但是呢
But, uh...
我来还个价吧
Let me make you a...counteroffer.
快看这个
Look at that.
猴子穿上衣服还真是可爱
It's so cute when monkeys wear clothes.
我在做梦吗
I'm dreaming, aren't i?
自从你像胆小鬼似的躲起来后
It's the only way we could chat...
这是我们唯一能进行交流的方式
Since you're hiding like cowards.
难得看见你独行
Don't normally see you off leash.
你老大呢
Where's your boss?
卡西迪奥吗
Castiel?
他
Oh, he, uh...
不在这儿
He's not here.
知道吗  他也有弱点
See, he has this weakness.
他喜欢你
He likes you.
时间到了  小子
Time's up, boy.
交出女孩
We want the girl.
换做是我就不会这么做
Wouldn't try that if I were you.
知道吗  她重获能量了
See, she got her grace back.
现在是风韵十足的天使了
Full-blown angel now.
要知道我还握着她的能量呢
That would be a neat trick, considering...
别想耍花招
...i have her grace right here.
我们不能让地狱得到她
We can't let hell get their hooks into her.
那么  为啥你不把天使能量还给她呢
Well, then why don't you just give her back her angel juice?
她犯了重罪
She committed a serious crime.
怎么了  就因为她自己着想了吗
What? thinking for herself?
这是我们的事  不关你事
This is our business, not yours.
某种意义上讲她还不能算是人
She's not even human... not technically.
是吗  我猜自己只是个屁
Yeah, well, I guess I just like being a pain in the pooper.
不对
No.
还不止
There's more.
你把自己变成
You cut yourself a slice of...
一块蛋糕
Angel food cake.
是这样吧
Didn't you?
确实如此
You did.
你担心什么
What do you care?
你也不过是个废物
You're junkless down there, right?
像个傀儡
Like a ken doll?
你最后的机会
Well, it's your last chance.
-交出女孩  不然  -不然怎样
Give us the girl, or -- or what?
怎样  你要把我扔回地狱吗
What, you're gonna toss me back in the hole?
少唬弄人了
You're bluffing.
不信试试
Try me.
这可比有关你的计划来的重要的多  迪恩
This is a whole lot bigger than the plans we got for you, dean.
你可被取代
You can be replaced.
搞什么鬼东西
What the hell?
只管放马过来
Go ahead and do it.
你确定要回地狱吗
You're just crazy enough to go, aren't you?
我还能说什么  我绝不轻易妥协
What can I say? I don't break easy.
好吧
Oh, yes...
你确实如此
...you do.
你只是该清楚哪里才能撒野
You just got to know where to apply the right pressure.
知道你们这代人的问题在哪儿吗
You know the problem with your generation?
太易于满足
Instant gratification.
注重现在
It's all now, now, now.
毫无耐心  没有技艺
No patience, no craftsmanship.
但我不得不说
But I do have to say...
你的这把刀
This knife of yours...
还真是件好东西
It's an exquisite piece.
告诉我哪来的
You must tell me where you found it.
知道吗
You know...
自去波特兰以来 我好久没来这儿了
I haven't been up here since poland '43.
事实上  我厌恶这儿
Truth is, I loathe it.
寒心的很啊
It's chilly.
没有血腥味  鲜肉的滋滋声  剥皮后的湿粘
No stink of blood or sizzle of flesh or the wet flap of flayed skin.
我都不知道你怎么忍受的
I don't know how you stand it.
你越早合作
So, the sooner you cooperate,
我就越早解决这恐怖的
The sooner I can finish up with this ghastly
天使任务  回家修行
Angel business and return home to my studies.
但别急
But no rush.
让我们来好好
Let's take our time...
品味这一刻
Relish the moment.
现在  我要移开这个 别和我词不达意的
Now, I'm going to remove this, but don't you go smoking out of that meat.
得逞不了的
You won't get very far.
现在你来告诉我天使在哪
Now you tell me where that angel is.
不要
No.
No?
不要
No.
我一告诉你  你就会杀了我
I tell you, you kill me.
但我可以带你去
But I'll show you.
我搞不明白  伙计
I don't know, man.
露比去哪了
Where's ruby?
她可是你的地狱密友啊
Hey, she's your hell buddy.
现在喝酒有点早  不是吗
Little early for that, isn't it?
在某处现在才是凌晨两点
It's 2:00 a.m. somewhere.
你还好吗
You okay?
是的  当然
Yeah, of course.
你好啊  安娜
Hello, anna.
很高兴见到你
It's good to see you.
怎么会
How?
你们怎么找到我们的
How did you find us?
迪恩
Dean?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
为什么
Why?
因为这是他们让他做得选择
Because they gave him a choice.
他们要么杀了我
They either kill me...
要么就杀了你们
Or kill you.
我知道他们是如何打如意算盘的
I know how their minds work.
你的选择是对的
You did the best you could.
我不会责怪你
I forgive you.
好吧
Okay.
不会再有诡计
No more tricks.
也不会再逃跑了
No more running.
我准备好了
I'm ready.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
不  你不需要道歉
No. you're not.
真的不需要
Not really.
你根本不懂感情
You don't know the feeling.
至少  我们曾经经历的那一切
Still, we have a history.
-这只是  -命令就是命令
-It's just - orders are orders.
我明白的
I know.
请快点动手
Just make it quick.
休想碰那个可怜的姑娘一根头发
Don't you touch a hair on that poor girl's head.
你怎么敢进这个房间
How dare you come in this room...
你活得不耐烦了吗
You pussing sore?
真粗俗
Name-calling.
那真是太伤害我的感情了
That hurt my feelings...
你们假装神圣  其实是狂热的激进份子
You sanctimonious, fanatical prick.
现在马上转身离开
Turn around and walk away now.
没问题  只要给我们那个姑娘
Sure. just give us the girl.
我们保证会让她得到应有的惩罚
We'll make sure she gets punished good and proper.
你知道我们是谁  更知道我们的能耐
You know who we are and what we will do.
我不会重复第二次的
I won't say it again.
立刻离开
Leave now...
否则我们就废了你们
Or we lay you to waste.
我想我想冒险试试
Think I'll take my chances.
抱歉  孩子
Sorry, kiddo.
为什么不跑回你爸爸怀中去呢
Why don't you go run to daddy?
咒语
Potestas inferna, me confirma.
Potestas inferma, me confirma!
迪恩  迪恩啊  迪恩
Dean, dean, dean...
我真是太失望了
I am so disappointed.
你答应过我什么来着
You had such promise.
不
No!
闭上你们的眼睛
Shut your eyes.
Shut your eyes!
闭上你们的眼镜
好了  你们这些家伙在等什么
Well, what are you guys waiting for?
去找安娜啊
Go get anna...
当然  除非你们怕了
Unless, of course, you're scared.
这可没结束
This isn't over.
噢  在我看来都结束了  废物
Oh, it looks over to me, junkless.
你没事吧
You okay?
不算太坏
Not so much.
什么事让你耽搁了这么久才来
What took you so long to get here?
抱歉因为和恶魔交易所以来迟了
Sorry I'm late with the demon delivery.
我只是受了点折磨
I was only being tortured.
我不得不称赞你  萨姆
I got to hand it to you, sammy.
让他们这一次都聚到了一块儿  天使和恶魔
Bringing them all together all at once -- angels and demons.
这真他妈的是个好计划
It was a damn good plan.
是的  当哥斯拉和巨蛾都追着你不放的时候
Yeah, well, when you got godzilla and mothra on your ass,
你想摆脱他们的最好方式就是让他们互相残杀
Best to get out of their way and let them fight.
对  你现在是在放马后炮
Yeah, now you're just bragging.
那么  我猜她现在应该是个一流的天使了  对吗
So, I guess she's some big-time angel now, huh?
她一定很高兴  无论她在哪儿
She must be happy... wherever she is.
我可不认为
I doubt it.
再说一次
Again.
我知道你听到他说的了
I know you heard him.
谁
Who?
阿拉斯泰尔
Alastair.
还有他说的
What he said...
关于我的承诺
About how I had promise.
我听到了
I heard him.
你不好奇吗
You're not curious?
迪恩  我好奇得要命
Dean, I'm damn curious.
但是你如果不想和我我谈地狱的事  我不会逼你的
But you're not talking about hell, and I'm not pushing.
那可不止四个月  你知道的
It wasn't four months, you know.
什么
What?
在人间是四个月  但是在那下面
It was four months up here, but down there...
我也不清楚  时间和这里完全不同
I don't know. time's different.
那就像是有四十年那么长
It was more like 40 years.
天啊
Oh, my god.
他们
They, uh...
他们用各种方式将我扒皮  钻心  拆骨直到
They sliced and carved and tore at me in ways that you...
直到我粉碎殆尽
...until there was nothing left.
但是之后  刹那间
And then, suddenly...
我又毫发无伤的出现
I would be whole again...
就像魔术一样
Like magic...
接着他们又会再次重复这一切
Just so they could start in all over.
而阿拉斯泰尔
And alastair...
在每一天结束的时候
At the end of every day...
每一次结束的时候
Every one...
他都会来
He would come over.
他开出了个条件能让我离开行刑台
And he would make me an offer to take me off the rack...
由我去抓那些灵魂放到行刑台
If I put souls on...
由我来折磨他们
...if I started the torturing.
而每一天  我都告诉他我会坚持到新生
And every day, I told him to stick it where the sun shines.
整整30年来  我都这样跟他说的
For 30 years, I told him.
但我无法再忍受了 萨姆
But then I couldn't do it anymore, sammy.
无法忍受了
I couldn't.
之后我离开了那个行刑台
And I got off that rack.
上帝给予了帮助  我可以远离那一切了  而则我开始折磨他们
God help me, I got right off it, and I started ripping them apart.
我都不记得了我折磨过多少灵魂
I lost count of how many souls.
这  这就是我对他们干过的事
The -- the things that I did to them.
迪恩
Dean...
迪恩  听着  你坚持了30年
Dean, look, you held out for 30 years.
没人能像你一样坚持那么久
That's longer than anyone would have.
要我怎么说
How I feel...
这
This...
我内心深处
Inside me...
我希望不再记得那些  萨姆
I wish I couldn't feel anything, sammy.
我希望我不再记得那该死的每一件事
I wish I couldn't feel a damn thing.